Now that we've written all the parts of the Wikipedia crawler,
الآن بعد كتابة جميع أجزاء متتبع Wikipedia،
let's see if they work together.
لنرى ما إذا كانوا يعملون معًا.
I'll start the program and see what happens.
سأبدأ تشغيل البرنامج وأرى ما حدث.
Hmm, OK.
ها، حسنًا.
The program is running but it isn't printing anything quite yet.
البرنامج قيد التشغيل لكنه لا يطبع أي شيء حتى الآن.
I guess it's doing the crawling first and printing at the end.
أعتقد أنه يتتبع أولًا ثم يطبع في النهاية.
Let's wait.
لننتظر.
Oh, great.
أوه، رائع.
It's done, and it looks like it worked.
لقد تم الأمر، يبدو أنه يعمل.
We got from the Big Four British railway companies to Philosophy.
لقد وصلنا من شركات السكك الحديدية البريطانية الأربعة الكبرى إلى الفلسفة.
But you know, waiting all that time is kind of annoying,
ولكنكم تعلمون أن انتظار كل هذا الوقت أمر مزعج،
and if I think about it,
وإذا فكرت في الأمر،
there's no real reason to wait until the end of the program to print the article chain.
فليس هناك سبب حقيقي للانتظار حتى انتهاء البرنامج من طباعة سلسلة المقال.
Charlie and I planned it that way,
لقد خططته مع تشارلي بهذه الطريقة،
but now that I see the results in front of me,
لكن الآن وبعد أن رأيت النتائج أمامي،
I think it would be better if we printed the articles as they were visited.
أعتقد أنه سيكون من الأفضل أن نطبع المقالات أثناء زيارتها.
I'll make that quick change with a command line text editor.
سأجري هذا التغيير السريع باستخدام محرر نص سطر الأوامر.
You can also use your standard text editor.
يمكنكم أيضًا استخدام محرر النص القياسي لديكم.
First, I'll remove this print statement from the end of
سأزيل بيان الطباعة هذا أولًا من نهاية
the program and I'll put a new print statement in the while loop.
البرنامج وسأضع بيان طباعة جديد أثناء التكرار الحلقي.
Let's save this change and test it. Here we go.
لنحفظ هذا التغيير ونختبره. ها نحن ذا.
So it starts with a random article,
سيبدأ بمقال عشوائي،
then Karnataka, and here it goes.
ثم كارناتاكا، وسيكمل من هنا.
Cool. I think this is a lot more fun to watch. All right.
رائع. أعتقد أن ما نشاهده أمر ممتع جدًا. حسنًا.
The program works. You can find the completed version of this program below this video.
البرنامج يعمل. يمكنكم العثور على الإصدار الكامل من هذا البرنامج أسفل هذا الفيديو.